[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_01_SpeakLochnir",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 7,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_01_SpeakLochnir_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_Lochnir",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_01_SpeakLochnir_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@12A_MSQ_01_SpeakLochnir_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@12A_MSQ_01_SpeakLochnir_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_01_SpeakLochnir_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_01_SpeakLochnir_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_01_SpeakLochnir_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_01_SpeakLochnir_Obj_Response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_02_InnTutorial",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 7,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_02_InnTutorial_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_MB_Grace",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_01",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_02_InnTutorial_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@12A_MSQ_02_InnTutorial_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@12A_MSQ_02_InnTutorial_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_02_InnTutorial_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_02_InnTutorial_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_02_InnTutorial_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_02_InnTutorial_Obj_Response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_03_VaultTutorial",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 7,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_03_VaultTutorial_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_MB_Grace",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_02",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_03_VaultTutorial_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@12A_MSQ_03_VaultTutorial_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@12A_MSQ_03_VaultTutorial_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_03_VaultTutorial_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_03_VaultTutorial_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_03_VaultTutorial_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_03_VaultTutorial_Obj_Response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_04_MeetPayne",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 7,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_04_MeetPayne_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_RegentJinJae",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_04",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_03",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_04_MeetPayne_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@12A_MSQ_04_MeetPayne_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@12A_MSQ_04_MeetPayne_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_04_MeetPayne_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_04_MeetPayne_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_04_MeetPayne_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_04_MeetPayne_Obj_Response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_06_ToMiclot",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 9,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_06_ToMiclot_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_AllyaMusa",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_06",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_04",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_06_ToMiclot_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@12A_MSQ_06_ToMiclot_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@12A_MSQ_06_ToMiclot_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_06_ToMiclot_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_06_ToMiclot_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_06_ToMiclot_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_06_ToMiclot_Obj_Response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_07_FreeMiners",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 9,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_07_FreeMiners_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_EliasDerit",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_07",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_06",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_07_FreeMiners_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@12A_MSQ_07_FreeMiners_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@12A_MSQ_07_FreeMiners_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_07_FreeMiners_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_07_FreeMiners_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_07_FreeMiners_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_07_FreeMiners_Obj_Response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_08_DestroyRune",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 10,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_08_DestroyRune_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_EliasDerit",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_08",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_07",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_08_DestroyRune_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@12A_MSQ_08_DestroyRune_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@12A_MSQ_08_DestroyRune_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_08_DestroyRune_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_08_DestroyRune_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_08_DestroyRune_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_08_DestroyRune_Obj_Response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_09_ReturnRegent",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 10,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_09_ReturnRegent_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_RegentJinJae",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_09",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_08",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_09_ReturnRegent_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@12A_MSQ_09_ReturnRegent_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@12A_MSQ_09_ReturnRegent_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_09_ReturnRegent_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_09_ReturnRegent_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_09_ReturnRegent_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_09_ReturnRegent_Obj_Response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 10,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_RegentJinJae",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_10",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_09",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Obj_Response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_alt",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 10,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_RegentJinJae",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_10",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_09",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Success_alt",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Obj_Response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_12_CampTutorial",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 10,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_12_CampTutorial_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_SerPayneBennett_03",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_12",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_10",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_12_CampTutorial_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@12A_MSQ_12_CampTutorial_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@12A_MSQ_12_CampTutorial_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_12_CampTutorial_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_12_CampTutorial_Obj_Proposal_Prompt",
        "InProgressResponse": "@NPC_DefaultDialogue_05_RegentJinJae",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_12_CampTutorial_Obj_Response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_13_StormBeach",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 11,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_13_StormBeach_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_SerPayneBennett_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_13",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_12",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_13_StormBeach_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@12A_MSQ_13_StormBeach_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@12A_MSQ_13_StormBeach_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_13_StormBeach_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_13_StormBeach_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_13_StormBeach_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_13_StormBeach_Obj_Response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_15_DefeatNavigator",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 12,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_15_DefeatNavigator_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_SerPayneBennett_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_15",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_13",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_15_DefeatNavigator_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@12A_MSQ_15_DefeatNavigator_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@12A_MSQ_15_DefeatNavigator_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_15_DefeatNavigator_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_15_DefeatNavigator_Obj_Proposal_alt",
        "InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_15_DefeatNavigator_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_15_DefeatNavigator_Obj_Response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_16_FastTravel",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 12,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_16_FastTravel_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_RegentJinJae",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_16",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_15",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_16_FastTravel_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@12A_MSQ_16_FastTravel_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@12A_MSQ_16_FastTravel_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_16_FastTravel_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_16_FastTravel_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_16_FastTravel_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_16_FastTravel_Obj_Response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_17_LochnirsNotes",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 13,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_17_LochnirsNotes_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_MB_Grace_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_17",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_16",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_17_LochnirsNotes_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@12A_MSQ_17_LochnirsNotes_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@12A_MSQ_17_LochnirsNotes_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_17_LochnirsNotes_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_17_LochnirsNotes_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_17_LochnirsNotes_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_17_LochnirsNotes_Obj_Response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_18_InspectStatue",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 14,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_18_InspectStatue_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_MB_Grace_04",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_18",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_17",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_18_InspectStatue_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@12A_MSQ_18_InspectStatue_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@12A_MSQ_18_InspectStatue_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_18_InspectStatue_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_18_InspectStatue_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_18_InspectStatue_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_18_InspectStatue_Obj_Response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_19_MeetPercilla",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 14,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_19_MeetPercilla_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_PercillaWallen",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_19",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_18",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_19_MeetPercilla_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@12A_MSQ_19_MeetPercilla_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@12A_MSQ_19_MeetPercilla_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_19_MeetPercilla_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_19_MeetPercilla_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_19_MeetPercilla_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_19_MeetPercilla_Obj_Response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_20_CollectCrown",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 15,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_20_CollectCrown_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_PercillaWallen",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_20",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_19",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_20_CollectCrown_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@12A_MSQ_20_CollectCrown_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@12A_MSQ_20_CollectCrown_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_20_CollectCrown_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_20_CollectCrown_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_20_CollectCrown_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_20_CollectCrown_Obj_Response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_21_FindGrace",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 15,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_21_FindGrace_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_MB_Grace_03",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_21",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_20",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_21_FindGrace_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@12A_MSQ_21_FindGrace_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@12A_MSQ_21_FindGrace_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_21_FindGrace_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_21_FindGrace_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_21_FindGrace_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_21_FindGrace_Obj_Response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_22_DestroyShrine",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 16,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_22_DestroyShrine_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_PercillaWallen_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_22",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_21",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_22_DestroyShrine_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@12A_MSQ_22_DestroyShrine_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@12A_MSQ_22_DestroyShrine_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_22_DestroyShrine_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_22_DestroyShrine_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_22_DestroyShrine_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_22_DestroyShrine_Obj_Response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_23_ToTower",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 16,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_23_ToTower_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_PercillaWallen_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_23",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_22",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_23_ToTower_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@12A_MSQ_23_ToTower_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@12A_MSQ_23_ToTower_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_23_ToTower_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_23_ToTower_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_23_ToTower_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_23_ToTower_Obj_Response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_24_DefeatGawain",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 16,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_24_DefeatGawain_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_PercillaWallen_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_24",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_23",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_24_DefeatGawain_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@12A_MSQ_24_DefeatGawain_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@12A_MSQ_24_DefeatGawain_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_24_DefeatGawain_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_24_DefeatGawain_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_24_DefeatGawain_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_24_DefeatGawain_Obj_Response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 17,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_RegentJinJae",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_25",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_24",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 17,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_00",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "MSQ_00_init",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_25",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_alt",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 17,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_00",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "MSQ_00_init",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_25",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Success_alt",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_01_PlaceFlowers",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 7,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_Side_01_PlaceFlowers_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_FionaMurphy",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_Side_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_Side_03",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_01_PlaceFlowers_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "@12A_Side_01_PlaceFlowers_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@12A_Side_01_PlaceFlowers_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_Side_01_PlaceFlowers_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_Side_01_PlaceFlowers_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@12A_Side_01_PlaceFlowers_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_Side_01_PlaceFlowers_Obj_Response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_02_GatherGift",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 7,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_Side_02_GatherGift_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_EddaYonkers",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_Side_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_04",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_02_GatherGift_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "@12A_Side_02_GatherGift_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@12A_Side_02_GatherGift_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_Side_02_GatherGift_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_Side_02_GatherGift_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@12A_Side_02_GatherGift_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_Side_02_GatherGift_Obj_Response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_03_CollectPicks",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 7,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_Side_03_CollectPicks_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_CemalQadir",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_Side_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_04",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_03_CollectPicks_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "@12A_Side_03_CollectPicks_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@12A_Side_03_CollectPicks_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_Side_03_CollectPicks_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_Side_03_CollectPicks_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@12A_Side_03_CollectPicks_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_Side_03_CollectPicks_Obj_Response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_04_ExplodeBarrels",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 9,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_Side_04_ExplodeBarrels_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_AsheDubois_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_Side_04",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_12",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_04_ExplodeBarrels_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "@12A_Side_04_ExplodeBarrels_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@12A_Side_04_ExplodeBarrels_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_Side_04_ExplodeBarrels_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_Side_04_ExplodeBarrels_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@12A_Side_04_ExplodeBarrels_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_Side_04_ExplodeBarrels_Obj_Response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_05_ArtifactShards",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 11,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_Side_05_ArtifactShards_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_HugoMolina",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_Side_05",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_16",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_05_ArtifactShards_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "@12A_Side_05_ArtifactShards_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@12A_Side_05_ArtifactShards_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_Side_05_ArtifactShards_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_Side_05_ArtifactShards_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@12A_Side_05_ArtifactShards_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_Side_05_ArtifactShards_Obj_Response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_06_GatherJewels",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 11,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_Side_06_GatherJewels_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_OldeGeiser",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_Side_06",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_16",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_06_GatherJewels_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "@12A_Side_06_GatherJewels_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@12A_Side_06_GatherJewels_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_Side_06_GatherJewels_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_Side_06_GatherJewels_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@12A_Side_06_GatherJewels_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_Side_06_GatherJewels_Obj_Response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_07_ForgeRing",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 12,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_Side_07_ForgeRing_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_JeongNabi",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_Side_07",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_19",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_07_ForgeRing_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "@12A_Side_07_ForgeRing_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@12A_Side_07_ForgeRing_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_Side_07_ForgeRing_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_Side_07_ForgeRing_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@12A_Side_07_ForgeRing_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_Side_07_ForgeRing_Obj_Response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_08_GatherFangs",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 12,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_Side_08_GatherFangs_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_HamzaKillic",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_Side_08",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_19",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_08_GatherFangs_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "@12A_Side_08_GatherFangs_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@12A_Side_08_GatherFangs_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_Side_08_GatherFangs_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_Side_08_GatherFangs_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@12A_Side_08_GatherFangs_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_Side_08_GatherFangs_Obj_Response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_09_CollectGlass",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 14,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_Side_09_CollectGlass_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_OliviaBarovier",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_Side_09",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_19",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_09_CollectGlass_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "@12A_Side_09_CollectGlass_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@12A_Side_09_CollectGlass_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_Side_09_CollectGlass_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_Side_09_CollectGlass_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@12A_Side_09_CollectGlass_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_Side_09_CollectGlass_Obj_Response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_10_BreakCurse",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 14,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_Side_10_BreakCurse_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_HugoMolina_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_Side_10",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_Side_05",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_10_BreakCurse_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "@12A_Side_10_BreakCurse_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@12A_Side_10_BreakCurse_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_Side_10_BreakCurse_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_Side_10_BreakCurse_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@12A_Side_10_BreakCurse_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_Side_10_BreakCurse_Obj_Response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_11_ClericAmulets",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 15,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_Side_11_ClericAmulets_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_DayoMusa",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_Side_11",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_21",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_11_ClericAmulets_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "@12A_Side_11_ClericAmulets_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@12A_Side_11_ClericAmulets_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_Side_11_ClericAmulets_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_Side_11_ClericAmulets_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@12A_Side_11_ClericAmulets_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_Side_11_ClericAmulets_Obj_Response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_12_KnightsCrest",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 17,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_Side_12_KnightsCrest_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_AsheDubois",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_Side_12",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_21 \u0026\u0026 12A_Side_04",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_12_KnightsCrest_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "@12A_Side_12_KnightsCrest_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@12A_Side_12_KnightsCrest_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_Side_12_KnightsCrest_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_Side_12_KnightsCrest_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@12A_Side_12_KnightsCrest_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_Side_12_KnightsCrest_Obj_Response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_13_DevilHoney",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 7,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_Side_13_DevilHoney_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_GeertieLother",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_Side_13",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_04",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_13_DevilHoney_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "@12A_Side_13_DevilHoney_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@12A_Side_13_DevilHoney_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_Side_13_DevilHoney_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_Side_13_DevilHoney_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@12A_Side_13_DevilHoney_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_Side_13_DevilHoney_Obj_Response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_14_CollectWine",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 9,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_Side_14_CollectWine_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_GeertieLother",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_Side_14",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_Side_13",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_14_CollectWine_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "@12A_Side_14_CollectWine_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@12A_Side_14_CollectWine_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_Side_14_CollectWine_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_Side_14_CollectWine_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@12A_Side_14_CollectWine_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_Side_14_CollectWine_Obj_Response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_15_CollectResources",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 7,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_Side_15_CollectResources_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_CemalQadir",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_Side_15",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_Side_03",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_15_CollectResources_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "FALSE",
        "Title": "@12A_Side_15_CollectResources_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@12A_Side_15_CollectResources_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_Side_15_CollectResources_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_Side_15_CollectResources_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@12A_Side_15_CollectResources_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_Side_15_CollectResources_Obj_Response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_16_ToGoodUse",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 7,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_Side_16_ToGoodUse_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_CemalQadir",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_Side_16",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_Side_15",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_16_ToGoodUse_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "12A_Side_17_MarketBoard",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "FALSE",
        "Title": "@12A_Side_16_ToGoodUse_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@12A_Side_16_ToGoodUse_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@12A_Side_16_ToGoodUse_Obj_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_Side_16_ToGoodUse_Obj_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@12A_Side_16_ToGoodUse_Obj_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_Side_16_ToGoodUse_Obj_Response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_17_MarketBoard",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 7,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_Side_17_MarketBoard_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_Side_17",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_Side_16",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_17_MarketBoard_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "FALSE",
        "Title": "@12A_Side_17_MarketBoard_Obj_Title",
        "Description": "@12A_Side_17_MarketBoard_Obj_Desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "",
        "InProgressResponse": "",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    }
]
